guitartabsexplorer.com 2017-06-06

# GuitarTabsExplorer.com - Privacy statement

____Content __Privacy statement

The privacy of our visitors is extremely import to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information which is received and collected by GuitarTabsExplorer.com and how it is used. 

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

## Personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. 

## Changes To This Statement

Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed. By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use. 

## Contact Us

If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to webmaster@guitartabsexplorer.com. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention. 

**This Privacy Statement was last revised on February 7, 2012.**
